Great.
He took all of them.
My little brother is such a rascal.
When it comes to stuff like this,
that little fucker works fast.
Where is that little bitch right now?
Okay, take him now.
-Everyone back off!
-On the ground, right now!
Cell phones off. Turn off your phones.
Stand back! Get back, everybody!
Hey! Shut the back door!
-Everyone over here.
-Turn off your phone.
Everyone, please turn off your cell phone.
Hey, be careful over there! Look out!
A weapon?
Hey, we need to sweep the tables
on both sides of the room.
Get all the evidence we can.
No stone unturned.
Yes, sir.
Hey, old timer! Sang-ung!
Hey, are you okay? Are you…
Are you hurt?
No. Are you all right?
Yeah. Get up. Hurry. Let's go.
Out of the way!
Get those two.
-Hey. Get down. Hurry!
-Uh, what? Why?
The cops. We can't get caught.
We have to leave now.
Kang Sang-ung?
We have to get out of here.
Oh, that pipe was in our way.
-Yep.
-Oh God.
Here. Take the bag.
Where are you going?
I have a dinner.
Formal meeting with my in-laws.
I'm late.
Hang on. Wait.
Huh? What is it?
Uh…
There.
A good first impression
with your future in-laws is crucial.
This kind of thing
is why our jobs are so hard.
I wish there was
an easier sense of balance in our work.
But having special powers
means your personal life
won't be easy or normal.
That's your burden.
Better head out.
See you later.
See ya.
Gosh! Finally, he's here!
Oh.
I'm with the police.
You're Ms. Kim, correct?
Yes, Kim Min-suk. What can I do for you?
I need to find Kang Sang-ung.
I was about to call and file a report.
I have no idea where he is.
Kang Sang-ung is currently a suspect
in an active investigation,
so we need your cooperation here.
Detective, please.
He's completely normal. That's the truth.
What, the police really believe
all these online rumors too?
So, what? You think he suddenly gets
superhuman strength
when he's holding cash or whatever?
You're smarter than that.
Right, Detective?
Superpowers? Yeah, right.
It's so ridiculous.
I know you're all hiding over there!
Well, I hope
you're all getting overtime tonight!
Let's say it's true.
Imagine Sang-ung really did have
a unique gift like that.
To use it…
he'd only spend his own money.
And he'd do it to protect others.
And help anyone who needs it.
He'd punish muggers and criminals.
He'd do a better job than you guys.
You collect overtime,
and never catch anyone.
So now you're going to arrest a man
making our streets safer.
He's doing your job
while you watch from the sidelines!
I'm sorry.
I said don't be late, Sang-ung.
But you told me it would all be okay.
Clubbing is pretty tiring. God.
Sang-ung can get through
that dinner, right? I feel so anxious.
Yeah, I know.
Do you think that her folks
will approve of his tattered jacket?
No idea.
I wonder who called those detectives.
Wait. I assumed that was you.
I didn't call.
It was me.
It's so important
to report illegal activity.
Bun-mi.
I haven't committed a crime, sir.
I told you to lay low, Sang-ung.
Said I'd lock you up if I saw you again.
Come on. Don't you have powers?
That's why I have to do this.
You think you're above the law?
Think you're righteous?
You know that saying?
"The road to hell
is paved with good intentions."
It's cliché 'cause it's true.
Because of you,
more people are gonna end up getting hurt.
And you keep on
sitting around doing nothing.
I feel you.
I wanna sit on the couch
and put the news on,
get pissed off at criminals,
shout at the screen,
and then go off to bed.
I couldn't live with myself if I did that.
With our powers, we can fight.
Don't you think we have a responsibility
to protect the innocent?
You were almost right before.
Except when we do nothing,
that's when people get hurt.
You're gonna be indicted.
Sang-ung.
Sang-ung!
Hang on! Wait.
TO MR. KANG SANG-UNG
FINAL OVERDUE NOTICE
PRINCIPAL DEBT: 25,000,000 WON
Twenty-five mil…
You gotta be kidding.
"Jeongja Loans."
Kang Sang-ung, you have a visitor.
Thanks. Much appreciated.
You look pretty good.
Pleasant place, huh?
I'm sure you could crash here
if you're jealous. Bottom bunk's yours.
Nah. I've always liked
living alone, actually.
If you only knew how hard I had to work
to make you into who you are today.
Oh, you have no idea.
-Somebody help me!
-Not so fast.
MUNDANE
I see all that you do.
Helping all those people,
always in secret.
That's the kind of hero
we need in the world.
HOTTEST AFFORDABLE SPEC-UP
DEALER: HERMES
At the end of the day,
no matter what you do,
I control everything, Sang-ung.
Later today, we're gonna help you escape
before your hearing.
So just try to play it smart.
Kim Min-suk.
That's her name, right?
You put a hand on Min-suk,
and you're dead.
JEONGJA LOANS
MUNDANE
Oh my God.
So where are we going?
We're going to your pretrial hearing.
DETENTION AND RELEASE WARRANT FOR SUSPECT
Hey. I thought you'd be nicer.
MUNDANE
Any funny business,
I'll blow your head off.
I have to find a way to get out of here.
Min-suk is in danger.
ETA five minutes.
This way.
Please bear to your right and go around.
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
APOLOGIES FOR THE INCONVENIENCE
Hold your breath.
Shit, I'm so screwed.
Hello, Min-suk, what is it?
Uh, hello, Chairwoman.
You sent my husband a debt notice.
I just found it.
Yes. And?
Has this been going on for a while?
And am I the collateral?
There's something you should know.
You're about to lose your collateral.
You might wanna send someone to kidnap me.
No, wait.
-Get rid of these guys.
-Easy work, boss.
You're safe now, honey.
It's been a minute.
Wait a second.
What exactly is going on here?
Why are these guys with you?
It's just how it worked out.
Huh?
Well, this is a rather awkward situation.
I think I felt more comfortable
in my holding cell.
Great.
The charges against you will be dropped.
The investigation is closed.
I did great, didn't I?
-You can't trust this woman, okay?
-You don't have to trust me.
You just have to trust
that I loathe Jo Nathan.
I hate him more than you.
A lot more. I guarantee you that.
All right, I did what you asked.
I saved Sang-ung.
So you're gonna do me a solid.
Jo Nathan's finished.
Take him out.
Are we just gonna stand by
while this spirals out of control?
Why'd we get into this?
It was to keep things quiet
and rake money in.
The press and the police are
circling like vultures.
We can't lay low and ignore it any longer.
That stupid brat completely ruined--
You maniac.
So loud.
Oh. What the hell?
"It's the bleeding of the masses
that allows our coffers to fill up."
Blood creates money.
So we have to shed it.
You haven't caught Sang-ung.
You're not stalling deliberately?
Of course not.
Sorry, Father,
but I have a favor to ask you.
This is the last time, all right?
I'll make sure to handle it quietly.
Gimhae Savings Bank.
So what does some bank have to do
with taking out Jo Nathan?
The truth is, my father doesn't exactly
trust me like he used to,
so he chose to move
the superpower ampoules there en masse.
And I'm guessing the three of us
just have to believe you?
If I was wrong about this,
I'd have very serious problems.
Trust me. The intel has been verified.
The truth is,
the Food and Drug Safety Ministry
is announcing a drug
which just got approved.
Once it's on the market, it's all over.
For your society, for us,
and every innocent citizen on earth.
How about that?
She's suddenly shedding a tear
for world peace.
So we're supposed to steal the ampoules
to stop the development of this drug?
Well, they were yours originally,
so you have every right.
There's a vault hidden inside.
I'm going to give you directions to it.
Morning, sir.
It looks like a normal bank,
but it's really one big safe deposit box
for the Mundane Vanguard.
Which means
the place is crawling with security.
The entire staff
is part of the Mundane Vanguard,
so it's important you prevent
the exposure of your identities.
This key will give you access
to the personal safety deposit boxes
on the basement level.
That's the easy part.
On the far side of that room,
you'll see the secret vault.
But, uh, I'm afraid
getting in won't be so simple.
A biometric signature from my father
is required to open the door.
Luckily, you guys are a special crew.
You got this, right?
The three of you get
to save the whole world,
Jo Nathan will get what he deserves, and…
I return as the rightful heir.
JO ANNA
HEIR TO BEOMHA GROUP
You sure Jo Anna isn't just using us?
Of course she is.
She's just exploiting us
to get rid of Jo Nathan
and to steal back the superpower ampoules
after the bank heist.
And after that,
she'll capture us and take us to Won-do.
She'll show up after we enter the bank.
Our first goal is to get her off our tail.
If you knew,
why'd you both agree to do the job?
It just so happens to be worth the risk.
Just like Jo Anna said.
If we get the superpower ampoules,
we have a shot at stopping Jo Nathan.
Also, Gimhae Bank is vital
to the Mundane Vanguard.
Don't worry.
I assume the Vanguard started accumulating
gigantic amounts of money
the minute they found out
about your powers.
We'll find their money and burn all of it.
If we do it right,
we could cripple them completely.
Hey, Sang-ung,
why did you agree to do this?
Easy.
She said I could get rid of
that bastard Jo Nathan.
That's the reason.
Good enough for me.
Look, we should go in here.
I'll start by scoping out
all the security cameras.
Ho-in, you'll enter first…
Please, don't go.
Why not?
I don't know if you were listening
to what their plan was, Sang-ung.
All you are is bait to these guys.
Yeah, I mean, what else is new?
-I still have to do it.
-Kang Sang-ung.
What?
FINAL OVERDUE NOTICE
-Uh, wait, how'd you get this?
-I work for Jeongja.
-Why on earth would you work there?
-It's not an accident.
You took out a private loan
behind my back.
You ruined the family dinner too.
Now, we're completely broke,
and I'm being held as collateral.
But you know what?
It's fine. I don't care.
We'll be able to pay it back eventually.
We're actually better off with you using
your own money to get stronger.
But this is different.
I think you know that.
You're risking our lives
to put up a fight against the Vanguard.
I can't do it. I'm sorry.
Min-suk.
I want a normal, happy life too.
I want quiet harmony.
Waking up early together.
Seeing you off to work.
And when the day's over,
we can set the table for dinner.
That's the life I want to build.
What are you saying?
That's why I have to go.
What I do…
it's not just about us though.
I want everyone to be safe.
To wake up every day with a chance,
a real chance at peace and true happiness.
It's a calling.
I'm the only one who can do it.
So how much do you need?
To put a stop to all of it.
To finish the job and walk away.
Just tell me. I'll get the loan.
JEONGJA LOANS
What is it?
EXPENSE REPORT
PAYMENT: CASH
KIM MIN-SUK
OPERATING EXPENSES: 30,000,000
Tell me why I should give you a loan.
Sang-un is going to Gimhae,
and he's a little…
Well, he's broke, ma'am.
Why are you getting me involved in this?
You know, I think I recognized
the address he's going to.
It looks like a normal bank,
but it's really one big safe deposit box
for the Mundane Vanguard.
Which means
the place is crawling with security.
It's Jeongja Loans' original location.
HEAD OFFICE MOVED
FROM 148-31 BUGOK-DONG, GIMHAE-SI
JEONGJA LOANS
So you planned to send him there
all along, didn't you?
That's why you approached Sang-ung.
He has…
He has such a good heart.
He wants to go.
I just can't let him go empty-handed.
I don't know what your angle is,
but if you wanna give him orders,
you're gonna have to put money
in his wallet first.
If you don't pay us…
I won't let him go.
One thing's for sure.
Sang-ung chose an outstanding wife.
LEE JEONG-SU, HEAD OF JBC
PRO-BEOMHA
We have a responsibility
to protect the innocent!
You were almost right before.
Except when we do nothing,
that's when people get hurt.
That little shit
has absolutely no idea
what he's up against here.
-Yeah?
-Here's the report from the club raid.
Don't you think we should think about,
uh, opening a side case
and getting a warrant to arrest Sang-ung?
I'm good with that.
This guy. What's the deal with Beomha?
You think he has a connection?
That dance club and the ranch he was at,
they're both owned by Beomha, sir.
BEOMHA RANCH FIRE
DATE: APRIL 23, 4 P.M.
BEOMHA RANCH, HWASEONG
MECENAT CLUB DRUG CASE
OWNED BY BEOMHA
JEONGGYE-DONG FIRE AND BRAWL CASE
BEOMHA RANCH FIRE
MECENAT CLUB DRUG CASE
You heard
of secondary cuts before?
-Huh?
-What?
When a pig gets butchered,
the pig gets cut up into short ribs,
tenderloin, sirloin, et cetera.
In between all that,
there are trimmings
that don't make it into those categories.
Secondary cuts.
What are you saying?
Let's get some tomorrow. How's that sound?
Okay, where?
Gimhae.
A surprise?
30 million won.
Where'd you get this money?
Doesn't matter.
I wanna be able to put this all behind us.
When I see you after the job is over,
I have something fun to tell you.
Oh, come on.
Just tell me now. I mean, why not?
Don't wanna.
I'll tell you about it when this is done.
All right, sounds good.
See you later.
Okay. Good luck.
I'll use it wisely.
This is the heart of the Mundane Vanguard?
GIMHAE SAVINGS BANK
This dumpy building?
Why does it look like it's about to fall?
It may look like your typical rural bank.
The security system
is the best in the country.
Catch them as soon as
they come out with the ampoules.
Then I'll wrap them up in a bow
and deliver them right into Dad's hands.
And if things end up
taking a turn for the worse,
we're gonna need
to beat my brother to the punch
and grab Sang-ung.
However this goes,
I guarantee I'll end up winning.
That's correct, ma'am.
You can take your checkbook back now,
and I'll start processing that.
How can I help you, sir?
Ah. Please. Right this way, sir.
Thanks.
This doesn't look good.
There's no question that we're the bait.
All right, let's get started.
Customer number 15,
you may now come to counter two.
There's no turning back now.
If I'm gonna be the bait,
I might as well be good at it.
Hi there. How are you, sir?
What can I do for you today?
Well, I'd like to apply for a loan.
All right. Do you have a valid ID on you?
Kang Sang-ung. You know my name.
Everybody out! Get out now.
Outside! Let's go!
Please clear the area!
Exit through the front door.
Goddammit!
GIMHAE SAVINGS BANK
Gi, hurry. The alley door. Get inside!
Is everyone ready?
-I can fly
-Fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
-Try to fight
-Fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine
Give me all the cash
I feel the fire now
Try to punch you, smash
Devil is into your mind
I am cynical, but I feel powerful
I can crush you now
Time is done you better run
Let me whisper to your mind
You will feel the burn
Supernatural
I got the power on my mind
I can give you all the pain
Till the break of dawn
I can fly up the sky
Every day and night
Drop it on the floor
Better listen now
You got nothing
And I know that this is over now
Chasing you around
Round merry-go-round
Boo, I got you
You will never see the light
Let me whisper to your mind
You will feel the burn
Supernatural
I got the power on my mind
I can give you all the pain
Till the break of dawn
I can fly up the sky
Every day and night
Burn the lonely eyes
Crucify your lies
Now you cry
You better run
Run it speed of light
You better run, run it till you fight
Pain through your heart
Pain through your soul
It's time
-I can fly
-Fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
-Try to fight
-Fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine
No one else can find you now
Only devils on your side
You will see the darkest night
-I can fly
-Fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
-Try to fight
-Fly
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine